- Tonight on
"The Bachelorette"...
[all shouting]
- Hannah!
- I need a man that's
gonna be there with me
through all the pain.
[beeping]
And I mean all the pain.
- [screams]
[laughter]
- All the guys are making
me feel so good.
- Wanna feel it?
Behave, girl.
Behave.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
That is what
Mama used to say.
- Quite honestly,
you give me hope.
- Absolutely I feel like
I'm falling in love.
- I can't stop thinking
about you, and I love that.
That could be my wife
right there.
[uplifting music]
- You guys have
really good energy.
- She's kissing other guys.
It's not a easy pill to swallow.
I just need to get
something off my chest
with her real quick.
- Later, okay?
I need him to slow his roll.
- Luke's self-imploding.
- There's something I need
to discuss with Hannah.
- Cam told us that he was gonna
tell you a sad story
to kinda get the pity rose.
- This just feels real
schemy and slimy to me.
- Whoa.
- What just happened?
- This is my worst nightmare.
- Wait.
- They took her
to the emergency room.
- No way.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- It all happens
starting right now
on "The Bachelorette".
- Morning, fellas.
all: Morning.
- Uh, crazy night last night.
A lot to talk about.
First and foremost,
you guys kinda got to see
a different side of Hannah,
an emotional side.
all: Yeah.
- Definitely.
At last night's Rose Ceremony,
Hannah started breaking down
and she started crying.
She felt bad because
she's gonna have to send
some good guys home.
Things are gonna get real
from here on out.
Guys are gonna develop strong
connections with her
and it's gonna get
nothing but harder.
- So I think that
the takeaway from last night
is that she's really feeling it
and things are going really well
but your time with her
is fleeting.
So when you do get time,
take advantage of it.
You get two group dates
and another one-on-one date.
You guys have
a fun week ahead of you.
[chatter, laughter]
I'll see you guys soon.
all: Thanks, Chris.
- Let's do it.
[suspenseful music]
- Jonathan.
- Ooh. Okay.
- Matteo.
John Paul Jones.
Kevin.
Jed.
Tyler C.
Mike.
Cam.
♪ ♪
- Last week, Cam,
he didn't get chosen
to go on a date so Cam
crashed the group date,
which I thought was messed up.
- "Let's push our love
to the limit.
Hannah."
- We got Cam coming out today.
I feel like everyone's on edge
and ready for him
to cross those lines,
and I feel like
he's taking this bold thing,
like, way out of proportion.
Bold doesn't have to mean
being an [bleep].
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I have a great group
of guys.
Today we are going
to put them to the test.
Women go through a lot of pain,
and so it's important
that my man have sympathy and
empathy for what we go through.
These guys have no idea
what they're in for.
Hey!
Come--oh!
- Oh!
- Oh, Big Mike.
- All right, save some for us.
Save some for us.
Good to see you, Hannah.
- Hi, good to see you.
I've got something really
interesting in store for us.
So are y'all ready?
- Yeah.
- Good, come on.
- Let's go.
- Let's do it.
- The date card says, "Let's
push our love to the limits,"
so we're really gonna push!
- All right, baby, push.
Push, push, push!
- [screaming]
- Okay!
- Oh, my God, it's coming!
- You're crowning!
You're crowning!
Breathe, breathe, breathe!
- Oh...
- Here we go, here we go!
It's coming!
- [screaming]
- I see the head!
- Get it out of me!
- Oh, my God!
One more push!
It's here!
It's a boy!
- Oh, my God!
- [laughing]
- Oh, hey, guys.
- Oh, hey!
- We didn't see you there.
- Oh, hey, Hannah.
- Hey.
- Hey, so, come on over.
- Oh, God...
He's beautiful.
- Oh, thank you.
- Guys, I want a family one day.
And so I have some
friends over here--
Jason Biggs and Jenny Mollen.
- The guy from "American Pie."
- Hi, guys.
- It's Jason Biggs
and Jenny Mollen.
She's hilarious.
And now I'm really wondering
what in the world is in store
for us today.
- And, uh, they are going
to teach us a little something.
- We've got some fun
lessons in store.
- Activities.
- Activities, if you will.
Have a seat.
- I'm hoping that today
these guys learn the true
strength of a woman.
- Most men know how much fun
it is to make babies.
Well, except for Colton.
Am I right?
[laughter]
- Yeah.
- But obviously there
is a lot more that goes into it.
- So we want to see how familiar
you are with the female anatomy.
- Mm-hmm.
- I don't really know too much
about pregnancy but that
your belly gets bigger
and bigger
and the woman gets hungrier
and hungrier.
So, uh, you know,
I'm excited to learn what else
is going on here.
- Which organ does a woman
grow during pregnancy?
[quirky music]
All right,
let's see what you got.
- Uterus.
Well, no,
we always have the uterus.
Ovaries?
No.
Placenta
was the correct answer.
[all oohing]
- Oh, wow.
- Jed, nice work.
- Somebody knows his way
around a woman.
[laughter]
- How long is the gestational
period of a woman?
Nine months?
Nine months, correct.
Uh, two weeks.
- [laughing]
No.
- Good job, guys.
Most of you.
- Personally I'm not surprised
that Cam's struggling,
uh, when it comes
to female reproduction.
- Let's move on
to our next lesson.
- The pregnancy belly.
- Take it easy, baby.
Don't overexert yourself.
- Everyone feel pregnant?
- I didn't realize
it felt like, you know,
you're falling forward
all the time.
I could see how they talk about
their lower back hurting.
That was--that was insane.
- Just go ahead
and pick your baby.
This one's holding it
like a football.
- So we want to see
you guys diaper,
change,
and comfort your baby.
- Today we're experiencing
the trials and tribulations
of pregnancy--motherhood.
- Soothe your baby.
- My baby's crying right now.
He'll stop crying.
Eventually.
- I think today is really just
symbolic of what life is like.
- Oh, spilt milk.
- It can be messy.
- What is John Paul doing?
- And it can be painful.
- Breastfeeding can be
extremely painful.
I have brought
some clothes pins.
- Oh...
- Oh!
- That's just, like,
a part of life together.
Are you ready?
[laughter]
- [groaning]
- [shouting]
It was the worst pain
it could possibly be.
- Let's move on
to the next lesson.
- The final lesson.
- Until...
[dramatic chords]
- All righty then.
- Now we would like you
to experience the true joy
of childbirth
with this labor simulator.
- Oh, [bleep].
- So who would like to go first?
- Oh, step it up.
There you go, Kevin.
I like that.
- Baby, would you say labor
is the most intense pain
you've ever experienced?
- It's so painful
that you just, like, stop.
It's like a blackout.
- How accurate is this,
Doctor?
- I would say this
is pretty accurate.
- This is real.
- Now here we go.
The baby's coming.
[electronic whine]
- Oh!
Oh, my God.
- This might be a big one.
- Oh, [bleep]!
- Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God.
- It was, uh,
excruciatingly painful.
Much respect goes out
to you ladies.
- Oh!
Oh!
- Oh, gosh.
- [groans]
[laughter]
- Oh, my gosh!
Okay!
Oh, ow.
You're hurting my hand.
- Whoo!
- Ready to hang tight with me?
- I am.
- I just need you--
I'm gonna need you right here.
- Okay.
- I'm a chiller.
- I don't know if Tyler C.
knew exactly
what was going on,
but I'm pretty sure he thought
it was a photo shoot.
[electronic whine]
- Oh!
[laughter]
- Why can't you keep your arm
behind your head
all sexy like that?
- I'll keep it there.
- Go on.
You can do it.
- [groans]
[laughter]
- Oh, my God.
- I think he might actually
be giving birth.
[quirky music]
- Whoo!
- When, like, I got with Jed,
there was just, like,
an obvious connection
of just, like...
doing this together.
[electronic whine]
[both moaning]
It's okay, it's okay.
- Wow!
Whoo!
That really hurts a lot.
- Ah, don't do it!
Don't do it!
- Why are you already
doing that?
Nothing's happening.
- I can't, man.
- You got this,
John Paul Jones.
You got this.
- All right.
- But I don't know why you're
already, like, being like this,
because it's not on.
- All right, okay, all right.
- Come on.
[electronic whine]
Look, look.
You gotta look at me.
- [screaming]
[laughter]
- Oh, my God!
That's not fun--I'm--
[screaming]
[laughter]
- Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
[screaming]
That is my hand!
- Oh, my God.
[laughter]
- Thank you, Doctor.
- You know, today was fun
and laughs and hot men.
- But seriously I hope they
kinda see just how hard
and tough it is for a woman.
I think after that you all
deserve a cocktail.
So let's go to
the cocktail party.
Thank you, guys.
- Yeah, of course.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- All right.
- You're gonna need it.
[laughter]
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- Am I the only one here
that's sore?
- Your abs?
Oh, yeah.
- From the shock?
- Yeah, my abs are done.
- I appreciate y'all
still having
a smile on your face after.
So, cheers to a painless night.
all: Cheers.
Today was really fun.
But it was also painful
for the men,
so I want tonight to be just
a good relaxing group date
cocktail party.
- Hannah, can I grab you?
- Yeah, let's go.
All right.
I had so much fun
today with Jed.
I always have so much
fun with Jed.
- You want one?
- No, I'm good.
- All right.
I'll bring it for the road.
- Later.
- All right.
- It's really evident
that we already have
a really good connection.
I love, like,
that he's creative,
that he has big dreams.
It's so great to be with
somebody that's passionate
about something.
- Oh.
- It's really pretty.
- Yeah, it's beautiful.
I've never seen
a city this big.
- Well, Nashville's pretty big.
Right?
- Not really.
Have you been?
- No, but I wanna move there.
Isn't that the weirdest thing?
It's where I want to be.
- Well, you know,
maybe we can arrange that.
- That sounds good.
- Yeah.
It sounds great to me.
- I know a guy.
I know a guy.
- Yeah, I know this guy there.
He's pretty cool.
- Yeah.
- But, uh, our relationship
obviously is, like,
the most important thing to me.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I want to build that.
I want it to be about us.
Any time that I have.
And I want more of it.
And I'll do whatever
I have to do.
- Good.
Well, I noticed today.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- This whole thing is just--
it's blown my mind.
I could not have expected
to feel this way.
It just keeps getting more
and more real.
I believe it is good luck...
To make a wish.
- Okay.
- And you can't tell me
what the wish is
until I get a one-on-one.
- Okay.
- You gotta chuck this chicken
nugget off the roof
and make a wish.
All right, you ready?
- Yeah.
- Go.
Tonight I showed initiative
and dove into the whole
process of being with her.
♪ ♪
And I think she
appreciated it,
and I would say tonight
was for sure the first
real step in our relationship.
- I'm looking forward
to getting some more
one-on-one time tonight,
hopefully uninterrupted 'cause,
you know,
in totality I think I've had
the least amount of time,
um, with her, uh,
compared to most of you guys
who've had a couple
of group dates
or additional
one-on-one time with her.
You know, you don't wanna look
back and--and have regrets
about things that you could
have done differently.
You just have to do what you
feel is best for you
and Hannah's relationship,
not the other
guys' relationships.
- Can we agree, though,
if it was just a gigantic
free-for-all,
no one would get anywhere?
[percussive music]
You ever watched
first grade soccer?
Where they all follow the ball?
That's what it'd be like
if we just all stepped
on each other the whole time.
I mean, there's times where,
you know,
I gotta play the game right.
- Absolutely, man.
100%.
- You know what I mean?
- Totally.
Sure, man.
- You know?
That's it.
- That's it.
- Well, give me a hug.
Today we had an amazing date
around babies,
and it only made me think
of a situation I had
in the past with my ex--
something that...
really broke my heart.
Uh, you know me as a jovial,
energetic, enthusiastic,
always positive type.
And being quite honest,
I'm an extremely
confident individual.
I felt that you liked me
as a person.
- Mmm, absolutely.
- But there was
something missing
on our first rose night,
and one of the things that you
asked for was vulnerability.
[sighs]
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Okay.
- It, uh--
This is, uh, insight
to who I am.
- Okay.
- So I met my ex,
and we had got pregnant.
And when we got pregnant,
you gotta understand,
I had the engagement set.
I was just really ready
to start a family.
- Mm-hmm.
- But...we lost our child.
And so--
- When did you...
- We lost our child
in the second trimester.
[somber music]
And today I--it reminded
me of that.
It was my fault because
I wasn't there for her
at the time.
Thank you.
And--sorry, I can't--I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
- I'm so sorry.
- Appreciate you.
♪ ♪
It's a--it's a--it's
a terrible thing.
I--I--I, uh--
It's just one thing that
I could be a better man at.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you so much
for sharing that.
It shows me so much
about who you are.
- It was my faith
that kept me strong.
Um, right?
And...
Don't worry about nobody else.
It's just us.
- Hey, um, just whenever
you guys wrap up,
I'll just be outside.
Have a minute.
Thanks.
- And...
Never in my life have
I ever cried so hard.
Just--
This don't happen a lot.
- It's okay.
It's a big deal.
- Yeah, it is.
- To share your story.
- Um...
I'll--I'll come get you
in a second.
Can you walk outside the door,
please?
- I have something
really important, just,
whenever you--
can you wrap it up
a couple minutes here, please?
Thanks, man.
- Okay.
My apologies.
- It's okay.
- Quite honestly,
you give me hope.
You definitely do.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Thank you so much
for just listening to me.
- Absolutely.
- I just really appreciate it.
Thank you for sharing.
And I also wanna say,
um--
[footsteps]
♪ ♪
- I have something really
important I need to tell her.
Please, I haven't had any time.
Please.
- You're gonna get your time.
- Please, dude.
Now walk outside,
and I'll come get you.
- I promise.
- Hannah, okay.
All right.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Um...
- But, um,
just give me a hug, girl.
- [laughing]
- Give me a hug.
Mmm.
- Hey, man.
♪ ♪
- You have a good one, okay?
- Okay, thank you.
♪ ♪
Hey.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm great.
How are you?
- Good.
- Mike J., what's good?
- Yo.
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
gentlemen, gentlemen,
gentlemen.
- Something's up.
- Oh, I just got interrupted
three different occasions...
and twice,
Hannah as well said,
"You need to leave the room."
- To who?
- Cam.
He interrupted me three times.
Every 10--
Literally about 15 seconds
he walked back in there.
- Dude, insecurities
are showing, man.
- He said, "I have something
important to say,"
as if I didn't have nothing
important to say myself.
Sit your ass down and let me
have my moment with Hannah.
Because my moment
is important.
He's gonna quickly realize you
not gonna play that with me.
[dramatic chords]
[dramatic music]
- Cam interrupted
three different times.
If the woman that we're here
for needs to tell you
to calm down,
to walk outside as well--
- Respect my time,
I'll respect yours.
You know what I mean?
- Mm-hmm.
- He just doesn't get that.
- Yeah.
- And guess what.
She sees it,
and the writing's on the wall.
- Cam seems to like to cut
into someone else's time.
I mean, Cam also did it
in the group date last week.
You do something
to someone else,
it's gonna come back
and bite you.
- Is he in there now?
- Karma's a bitch, man.
- How are you?
- I'm so sorry, um--
- No, no, it's okay.
It's okay.
- Sometimes there's
conversations that, you know,
have to be had, so--
- I get it.
- Yeah.
- I'm a deep person myself.
And, you know, as much as I
love the lighthearted fun stuff
I think there's a very serious
side of me that you need
to get to know.
- Yeah.
- Because love is something
that's the utmost priority.
And if we're gonna talk
about bold gestures,
I actually had to resign
from my job.
And I want you to know that
I chose to be here for you,
and I don't want to let
any other guys get
in the way of that.
I value our time.
- Absolutely.
- Time, man.
- Hey, can I just have
two more minutes?
- Nah, I don't think so.
- Just two more minutes.
I literally just sat down.
- No, I think
it's about that time.
- Yeah, just two more minutes,
please.
I have to stay
for two more minutes.
- It's o--it's okay.
- No, two more minutes, man.
- It's--it's honestly
about that time.
I'm sorry, man.
It's, uh, just--what
goes around comes around.
- I'm--I really don't wanna
get up right now, dude.
- It's okay.
I know you don't want to.
- You had a group date already.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
- Yeah, well, I'll walk you
to the door.
- Okay.
- And then you can
stay right here.
- No, I'll take you out.
- Okay, okay.
[dramatic music]
I'm gonna walk her to the door,
and you can have a spot.
- All right, I'll take her out.
All right.
- I got it, man.
- No, it's okay.
I got you.
I got you, bro.
- All right, hey,
real quick, Hannah.
Let me give you a hug.
- Okay, thank you.
- You and I are gonna have some
more one-on-one time, okay?
- Okay, thank you.
- All right.
- Sorry.
Hey.
- How you doing?
- I'm good.
- I'm so sorry about that.
- It's okay.
I--
- It's a necessary
part of this.
So here we are.
How you doing?
- I'm doing good.
How about you?
- I'm feeling good.
♪ ♪
- He wouldn't leave.
- Really?
- And he goes, "What goes
around comes around."
And as I got up to escort her,
he literally got physically
in between us and wouldn't
let me even, like,
walk her to the door.
You know, there's a difference
between being bold
and being charismatic
and romantic
versus being just a little
physical overpowering
insecure Chihuahua
like he just was.
There's the saying that love
is worth fighting for.
But I'm not gonna
get physical.
So in this case, I had to be
the bigger man and walk away.
♪ ♪
- What's up, dude?
[lightly tense music]
♪ ♪
- You got something
you want to say?
No?
All right.
That's cool by me.
♪ ♪
Are you mad?
- Huh?
- Are you mad or no?
- No, I'm--I'm actually kinda
fascinated by it, man.
- Really?
How so?
- I just didn't think
that you had it in you.
- I know.
Me, neither.
- Good on you, good on you.
- Yeah, yeah, man.
- See how it turns out
for you, bro.
- Likewise.
♪ ♪
- Did you guys want
my chicken nuggets?
- No, that's--no.
- No.
♪ ♪
[knocking on door]
- [exhales sharply]
Here we go, boys.
♪ ♪
- To me the best thing that
could happen would be
to be on that one-on-one date.
Not having a date
last week was tough.
And, you know, I think it'd be
a great way to develop
a deeper connection.
♪ ♪
- Connor.
- Ooh.
♪ ♪
- "Let's set sail
on our love story."
[all oohing]
- Hey, buddy.
- Yeah.
- Nice.
- Yeah, I'm--I'm pumped.
I'm pumped.
- It's really frustrating
seeing these guys
go ahead of me.
But I'm not all too concerned.
There's some really
good guys here.
But I mean, she has
to compare them with me.
And I know that when
she does that,
she's gonna be like,
"Man, these guys are great,
but they're not Luke Parker."
[laughing]
♪ ♪
- Today--today made me
want to call my mama
and tell her I love her
because--
- Oh, that was sweet.
- Yeah.
Women really do run this world,
and they deserve
so much respect.
That's one thing
I will say about you
is that I see
this powerful woman,
and I firmly believe whatever
it is that your calling is
that you'll move mountains.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're a badass woman.
And that's, like,
one of the biggest turn-ons
about you,
and I want to be the one
that's fueling the fire.
And I mean that
with every ounce of me.
You know?
And I hope to be the guy
cheerleading next to you
and being your arm candy
and supporting you and...
- [laughing]
Thank you.
- I just--
- It's nice arm candy.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it tastes good, too.
[both laughing]
- Yeah, yeah.
- [laughing]
[mellow music]
- Tonight was
an amazing night.
She's captivating,
is the best way to put it.
You know,
I'm crushing hard on her.
Hannah is unreal.
♪ ♪
I'm not here to be just
another dude in the house.
I'm here to be Hannah's man.
So I want that rose tonight
more than anything.
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
- Tonight was so great
and, uh, much needed after
an incredible, fun day.
Uh, I feel like
every conversation
was really great tonight.
Uh, but I want to give
this rose to Mike
because bold can be shown
in many different ways,
and you showed another way
to be bold tonight.
So, Mike, will you
accept this rose?
- Southern belle,
of course I will.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
It has been a great night,
and I enjoy
every conversation we get
to continue to have.
So, good way to start the week.
- I feel like a million bucks.
I feel like a billion bucks
when you can be yourself
and you get rewarded for it
by being vulnerable
and--as she said--
being bold in my own way.
- Good night.
Y'all are awesome.
- Not feeling great right now.
Obviously would have liked
the Group Date Rose.
I had to resign from a job
that I worked very hard
to get.
To me that's the boldest
gesture you can do.
Definitely not
giving up on this.
I've never given up
on anything in my life.
I've always been a fighter
through and through.
And, you know,
love is worth fighting for.
- Coming up...
- You guys have really
good energy.
- She's kissing other guys.
It's not a easy pill
to swallow.
- Hey, you trying
to talk to Hannah?
- Yeah.
- All right,
that's not gonna happen
right now.
- He's very unstable right now.
- This right here
is--is annoying.
- Luke's slowly
self-imploding.
- 'Cause honestly I can't
stand this process.
I'm out of here.
[knocking]
- Hannah?
Hannah?
[sirens blaring]
They took her
to the emergency room.
- Wait.
- No way.
- Oh, gosh!
- This is my worst nightmare.
[sirens blaring]
- So I'll send this off
to the lab.
I'll get you some fluids
and I'll give you
the nausea medicine, too, okay?
Just in case.
We don't want you throwing up.
- It's just the fluids
or whatever?
- Yeah, it's just
a normal saline flush.
And then the fluids will be
that whole bag behind you.
Might feel a little cold
or salty taste in your mouth.
That's normal.
[dramatic music]
- You're still here?
- Yeah, dude.
Excited to get out of here.
- Ready to go.
- There's a reason
I'm on this date.
There's a reason I wasn't
on a date last week
and she saved this one for me.
The date card says,
"Connor,
let's set sail
on our love story."
I want so badly
to just sail away
into the horizon with Hannah
and spend as much time
with her as I can.
I feel like the luckiest
guy in the world.
[doorbell rings]
- Well, well, well!
♪ ♪
- Connor!
- Uh-oh.
- You got a delivery, bro.
- You got a delivery there,
Mr. Connor.
- Oh, man.
- Connor, my man!
- "Connor, I'm so sorry,
but I have to cancel my plans
"for our date today.
I'm not feeling 100%."
[dramatic music]
"Please come over to my hotel
suite to keep me company.
Love, Hannah."
[all oohing]
- All right, guys.
Gotta go, uh,
go see Hannah,
make her feel better.
- Yeah, go get her
better for us, man.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
- I'm sure there was
an amazing date planned.
It's definitely a bummer to not
have those original plans,
but what I'm excited about
is to kind of comfort her
and hopefully make her
feel better.
- Have a wonderful Sunday.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, you too.
- Uh-huh.
- You know,
there's gonna be days
where I'm sick or she's sick.
I want to be there
for each other
through the ups and downs
and, you know,
this is definitely
a down moment for her.
So, you know, hopefully
I can make her feel better.
♪ ♪
[knocking]
Hello.
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
- I'm good.
- Good to see you.
So nice to be here.
Sorry you're feeling
a little under the weather.
- Yeah, it's okay.
- Yeah.
- Come sit.
- Yeah, no, definitely.
- We're gonna hang out.
- Yeah.
[both laughing]
- It's about all I can do.
Cuddle up.
- Yeah.
- Hang out.
- No, definitely.
I got this card for you.
You don't have to read it now.
But--
- Do you want me--can I?
- Mmm, no.
- Ah!
- Maybe--maybe later.
- Well, I--
I want to read it.
- All right.
You can read it now.
- [laughs]
I'm not contagious so--
[both laughing]
- Wh--what's
feeling down today?
What's up?
You aren't 100%?
- Um, so I woke up and I just,
like, basically passed out.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
And went to the hospital and...
- Got pumped with some fluids.
I'm feeling better but not the
date we were supposed to have.
- [laughs]
No, no.
But, um, all I wanted to do
was just hang out with you.
You know?
- I'm so glad you came over.
- Yeah. No, we can still spend
time together now.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
- I'd be excited to have this
time with her if she was sick.
- I feel like it shows a lot
about you and how you can
care for her during one of her
tough moments, you know?
- Cuddling's like the best--
one of the best things to do,
you know, and you can still be
romantic, so...
- I'm anxious to see
how long it's gonna take.
Like, will she spend
four or five hours
or just one hour, you know?
It's my job to care
for her right now.
I really feel like, you know,
I know she wants me over there.
Honestly, I--if she
told me to leave,
I'd say, "It's all right.
"I'll just crawl up
next to you in bed
"and we don't
even have to talk.
I just want to be your--
you know, just be around you."
She makes me happy,
and I know that
just the thought of me
in her mind makes her happy.
I wouldn't leave.
[laughs]
[quirky music]
- Obviously, this whole
thing's really stressful
and tough to go through.
- Mm-hmm.
- And the other night I said
there are some, like,
kind of situations from my past
that made me who I am and...
- Mm-hmm.
- I think the biggest one is,
um, when I was 13,
I was skiing in Utah
with my family
and my mom ended up
falling over and, uh,
she ended up having a stroke.
Ended up airlifting her to, uh,
a hospital in Utah.
And I remember walking
in there with my brother
and trying to talk to my mom
and, um, she couldn't, like,
speak in a sentence and I just
remember leaving that room
and--and bawling.
You know, I was 13 and, uh,
you know, from that situation
I learned, you know,
how strong my parents'
relationship was.
Um, you know, I--
- You've said that.
- Yeah, I told you before
they've been married
for 37 years and, yeah,
they were married
when they were younger than us.
- Mm-hmm.
- And there are a lot of
ups and downs in life
and, um, you know,
sickness and health
and I think it just showed me,
like, that's really what
I aspire to have in my life
and--the love that I want.
- Thank you so much
for telling me that.
I can't imagine what
that was like.
But it is an honor to know,
like, what you've been through
and see how that shaped
the man you are today.
And I really like that man.
♪ ♪
- I feel amazing.
Obviously, it's disappointing
to see her not feeling well,
but just to be able
to spend time with her
means a lot to me and,
you know, I hope
it means a lot to her as well.
- I'm so sorry, but I have
to get back to sleep.
Doctor's orders.
- No, it's all good.
It's tough because, like,
I don't want to leave her.
Like, I want to be with her.
Especially now when
she's not feeling well.
♪ ♪
Obviously, I didn't get a rose
but when I do fall asleep,
I'm gonna have a smile
on my face just knowing
that I got to spend
a little bit of time
with such an amazing woman.
So I want to leave her
something behind
so she remembers the moment
and is thinking about me
when she wakes up.
♪ ♪
What's up?
- What's up, dude?
- Oh, do you have a rose on?
- Walking in
with that smile!
What's up with that strut,
boy?
- What's up, man?
- Like, how are her symptoms?
Like, was she coughing?
- No, so, she's not, like,
sick, sick in that sense.
Like she--she wasn't feeling
well and she actually just,
like, passed out, and so they
took her to the emergency room.
- No way.
- Yeah.
- You got a rose, clearly?
- No, so that was
the unfortunate thing.
But that's her decision,
and I have to trust that.
- I love Connor.
I think he's a great dude.
And he's gonna marry
an awesome woman one day.
But not Hannah.
Honestly, I think he's already
out of the picture.
[dramatic chords]
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- "Hannah, even though I did
not go sailing today,
"it meant so much more.
"This is how life will be
after all of this is over.
"It means so much
to spend time with you,
"and I want to leave
some notes behind
"of all the things
I love about you.
"Look around the room
to find them.
Love, Connor."
♪ ♪
"Your beautiful eyes."
"Hanging out
just like this."
"How pretty you look
without makeup."
"How mature you are."
[laughs]
I was surprised to find
all my notes from Connor.
It was fun to go on a hunt
throughout the room
and find all the things
that Connor loved about me
or that he's noticed about me.
"The sparkle in your eye."
Aww.
It's super sweet for him
to take that time
to show me how much he cares.
I loved it.
"Get well soon, Hannah.
Love, Connor."
That was so nice.
It's so sweet.
[quirky music]
- Did you have fun?
- Yeah, no, really good time.
[overlapping chatter]
- Yeah.
She has a cool hotel room.
- Really?
- You know, yes, it's fun
to hang out with the guys
and eat some food,
but I'm not here for that.
- You know,
high blood pressure,
which is really serious.
You know, you gotta watch that.
- Yeah.
I'm here to get to know Hannah
and find love with her.
It's definitely a bummer
to kind of not be able
to see her tonight.
- So, what was
she wearing, man?
Yoga pants, a big T-shirt?
- Yeah, just, like,
sweat pants, uh...
♪ ♪
Just, like, a T-shirt, yeah.
[door closes]
- Wait.
- Hey.
I'm looking for Connor.
- Yeah.
- Connor,
I'm here to pick you up.
Your date is not over.
Hannah wants you to be ready
in 15 minutes,
and be sharp, my man.
- Oh, [bleep].
[all shouting]
I did not expect that.
This has been a wild day,
but I think I've been able
to roll with the punches
and just be confident
about everything,
so honestly all I care about
is just seeing Hannah again.
- I mean, she's gonna feel bad,
regardless
who's getting the rose.
- Well, we don't want him
to get a sympathy rose.
[all speaking at once]
- This isn't a pity rose.
- Well, I mean, he is.
- Man, he said it is.
- Yeah, definitely.
[dramatic music]
- Yeah, I'm fired up
to see Hannah.
Tonight means she sees
a future in me,
and she wants to keep
getting to know me
and spend more time with me.
And even after a day
of ups and downs,
she wants to keep being there
for each other
through future ups and downs.
Oh, hello.
So good to see you again.
- It's good to see you, too.
- [laughs]
I didn't know
when I would again.
- [laughs]
Today was not what was planned.
- Mm-hmm.
- But it's not always the high
times but the low times, too.
And today you made me
feel so special.
Connor,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
Love to.
- Connor really
surprised me today
by just being able
to comfort me.
He left me sweet notes.
Connor made me feel so great
even though
I didn't feel great.
- Anticipation's
building here.
♪ ♪
- I want to be able to have
something special for him
since he was so sweet
with me today.
- ♪ There are days ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I wake up
and I pinch myself ♪
♪ You're with me
not someone else ♪
♪ And I'm scared
yeah I'm still scared ♪
♪ That it's all a dream ♪
♪ ♪
- Just being with Hannah
listening to a private concert
by Lukas Graham
singing "Love Someone",
it was just a magical moment.
- ♪ Even the worst ones
you make me smile ♪
♪ I'd stop the world... ♪
- Obviously it's a beautiful
song and I think, you know,
it's very telling to kind of
how our relationship has grown.
- ♪ But when you love someone ♪
♪ You open up your heart ♪
♪ When you love someone ♪
♪ You make room ♪
♪ If you love someone ♪
♪ And you're not afraid
to lose them ♪
♪ You'll probably never love
someone like I do ♪
- Absolutely I feel like
I'm falling in love.
There's obviously a strong
connection and, I mean,
today feels like a moment
I'll cherish
for the rest of my life.
- ♪ You'll probably never
love someone... ♪
- I did catch
the Hannah bug today.
I'm a little sick
with the Hannah fever.
- Coming up...
- I'm not seeing anybody,
so if you're, you know--
- You just hit on me.
- Today we're gonna see
what Hannah's guys do
in their secret lives
whenever she's not around.
- Demi did a great job
of finding the one
that needed to go bye-bye.
- And later.
- I just need to get
something off my chest
with her real quick.
- Later, okay?
- This right here
is--is annoying.
- He's very unstable
right now.
There's a fine line
between bold and desperate.
We're going to see
him implo--
- This week has been
a tough week.
It was draining emotionally
and physically.
Um, definitely had some drama.
I had to go to the hospital
and then I found out
Tyler G. had to leave,
and that's upsetting
because I really enjoyed
my date with him
and felt like our relationship
was at a really good place
and I wanted to explore
where that could go.
And even though this
is a tough situation,
I'm trusting this journey
and why I'm here.
So today I just want
to refocus,
reset,
and have a good time.
♪ ♪
[all shouting]
- Let's go.
- Yes!
- I'm ready, Hannah.
Let's go.
I'm fired up.
I get to see Hannah today
so I'm ready to go.
[all speaking at once]
- I'm going on
the group date today,
myself and seven other guys.
We got a date card
last night that said,
"A picture is worth
1,000 words."
I'm just happy I get the
chance to see Hannah today
and probably do something
really, really fun.
[all shouting]
- If it's anything like
it has been so far,
it could be physically beating
or embarrassing
but I'm willing to try
anything for Hannah.
- Today's gonna be really fun.
I have something exciting
planned for us.
So you wanna go check it out?
- Let's go!
I have eight men that are
hanging out with me today.
I'm so excited to get started.
I have a few tricks
up my sleeve
and we'll see how they do.
- Let's go!
Superstar!
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- What we got going
on in here?
- How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
- Grant.
- Great.
Franco.
Nice to meet you all.
You guys look amazing.
- So guys, this is Franco
and he's going to be
our creative director today
for our photo shoot.
So, you know, you can really
tell a lot about a guy
in how he works a camera.
Don't you think?
- Absolutely.
I really want to be able
to get to know who you are
as a couple working together
with somebody else.
So we have incredible
professional models,
and I've decided to pair them
up with who I think
could be a really
good chemistry.
- These are like top models.
- Yeah, they're top models.
- I just completely
did not expect this.
We have some photos
to be taken.
We're gonna be paired up
with some models
with Hannah watching.
It's gonna be weird.
- So this is how we begin.
- Gary, you're gonna be
sunbathing with Laverne.
Grant--
- That's me.
- Bath time with Priscilla.
[all cheering]
- Let's go!
- Luke P. with Sherry.
- It's gonna be a little
awkward if I'm standing
next to some beautiful
girls modeling.
I just hope this doesn't
get awkward for Hannah.
[laughs]
- So let's go.
- Go.
[clapping]
All right, have fun.
- Okay, guys.
Find your models.
[barking]
- No way!
- Yes!
- Oh, my God.
[yip]
- Come on!
- It smells really
good in here.
- We walked into
this huge room
filled with
the best pets ever.
And I'm the luckiest because
I get little Sally Sue here
and she's an absolute doll.
Okay. Okay.
[pig squealing]
[continues squealing]
- Okay.
My puppy.
Yeah.
- I have a snake.
I'm--
[snake hisses]
Hey, you guys wanna switch?
Anybody want a snake?
- So some of my favorite
pictures I've ever taken
have been with my two
Golden Retrievers.
So today we're going to draw
a little bit of inspiration
from the new movie
"The Secret Life of Pets 2".
- "The Secret Life of Pets 2"
is a fun movie.
It's really interesting
to really think about
what do pets really do when
you're not at home?
- I'm excited to hear what type
of pets the guys have
back at home because it really
tells you a lot about a man.
- Hey, you gonna help me
win over Hannah today?
Huh?
Yeah?
I think you will.
My dogs at home
are a little nicer,
but he's got a soft
side to him,
so reminds me
of my dogs at home.
- I have a Tibetan Terrier.
He's like 14 now.
Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
- He's my best friend.
You have two Goldens.
- Roscoe and Ellie.
She can play, like, football.
Like, catch it--
- Can she actually?
I love that.
- Yeah, so--
I miss my Golden Retrievers
so much and when I'm not around
they're definitely
up to no good.
I mean, we love our pets,
but how well
do we really know them?
I love my group of guys but
how well do I really know them?
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Let me get a shot
of the makeup artist room.
♪ ♪
"The Secret Life of Pets 2"
is about what pets do
in their secret lives whenever
their owners aren't around,
so today we're gonna see what
Hannah's guys do
in their secret lives
whenever she's not around.
I guess you could call this
the secret life
of Hannah's guys.
Grant looks scared--that snake
is bigger than his arm.
Hannah's mind is gonna be
totally blown.
I've got cameras set up
all over the place,
and I hired actors to play
an animal handler
and a makeup artist.
Nothing is gonna
get past me today.
- [laughs]
- Hannah!
- What the crap?
- Hi!
- You get to deal
with guys like us.
- [laughs]
Well, I don't always get to
work with hot studs but--
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- This is amazing.
- Anything for you.
I'm here to make sure that
these guys are here
for my Hannah.
- That's right, thank you.
- Like, the makeup artist
and the animal handler
that I "hired" are so cute.
And I was like, "flirt it up
with those dudes
and see if they crack."
- Yes.
Demi did a great job
the first night of finding...
the one
that needed to go bye-bye.
So I decided to bring her back
and get her insight
on who is not here
for the right reasons.
- Maybe if I become
famous one day
you can be my makeup artist.
- Oh, Grant, Grant, Grant.
- Well, I live here in town.
So if you're, you know,
it's not working out...
[laughs]
I don't know.
I'm not seeing anybody, so...
- [laughs]
- She's so good.
- You just hit on me
in front of me.
I'm calling Hannah.
- Aww!
- That's good.
That's good.
Can I please listen to Peter?
- I've never dated a girl
with so many other guys.
- Is she cool so far, though?
I mean, she seems cool.
- Oh, yeah.
She's a great girl.
- Right?
- It's--it's fun.
Get to do a photo shoot
with these guys now.
- Yeah.
- That's good.
- That's so sweet.
- That was really sweet.
I would be [bleep] if they
did this on my season.
Who knows what I would say?
Can we switch to Luke P.,
please?
He's in the makeup artist room.
Thank you.
- So what do you do
for a living?
I'm guessing something
with fitness.
- I do CrossFit.
- Oh, wow.
- But not for a living.
- Oh, oh, okay.
- If I found out that Luke P.
wasn't sincere
and wasn't here for me
and then said all this crap,
oh, bless his soul.
He needs to be breaking out
scripture now.
- Are you having fun in LA?
- Yeah, I mean, it's a blast.
I mean, it kinda sucks
we're at a cool mansion,
but we're just stranded there.
- Yeah.
- But I'm actually developing,
like, a genuinely real
relationship with this girl.
- Are you?
- That's good.
- Yeah, like I wanna
just go talk to her.
- Aww!
Well, I mean,
do you think you could
actually get engaged
with her?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Yeah, she's like
the perfect woman for me.
- Aww, I love hearing that.
That's so cute.
- Luke P. passed.
Luke P. passed the test.
- Damn.
- That was good.
- I've really seen a lot
of good stuff here
and I think you have
a great group of guys left.
I'm excited for you.
- I'm excited for me, too.
Demi, like, as much as she's
happy for me,
she is profoundly disappointed
that there's nobody
to stomp on,
but it is better
and more comforting
for me to know
that these guys
are actually great.
I love you.
- I love you, too.
[upbeat music]
- You're sunbathing.
Head up.
Face up, yeah.
There you go.
Perfect.
Now look at me.
- The guys are being really
tender and connecting
with their partner
in this photo shoot.
- I am alive!
- I'm loving this.
They're gentle and sweet
and trying to really get into
their role as a model today.
[laughs]
- Now have a true connection.
Look into each other's faces.
- Wow, you actually
do look beautiful, though.
- Aww, thank you.
- So this is pretty cool.
I think you should come in
a little bit closer.
- Oh, it's so sweet.
- Just a little bit.
[dramatic music]
Mmm.
- [giggles]
- She's kissing other guys.
It's not a easy pill
to swallow.
♪ ♪
[all oohing]
I mean, yeah,
it's frustrating.
Who wants to date someone
and start to fall in love
with someone
and have to share?
- Like, look at her like,
"Oh, you're riding me
and I love it."
[laughter]
- Grab his face like--
[grunts]
Squeeze the cheeks.
Oh, it's so nice.
You guys are great.
- Hey, I got one
more real quick.
- What, am I getting
kicked out of here?
- I'm gonna do some push-ups
and you're gonna balance
on my back.
- What?
- Just do you.
Just smile at the camera,
all right?
Just get on my back.
- Luke actually went back and
wanted to get more pictures
with Hannah when he was
doing some push-ups.
He's definitely
a pretty in-shape dude.
Luke, we get it.
We get it, Luke.
- Oh, I have to change.
I gotta change.
- Oh, do you?
Oh, okay.
- Yeah, one second.
- Well, hey, I can walk you
to your changing room.
[laughs]
Where you going?
- I don't--I think I have
to go over here.
- You just wanna talk a minute?
- Huh?
- Just wanna chat a minute?
- I don't--we can--
Let's talk tonight.
Okay?
- All right.
- Luke P. tried to grab me
after our photo shoot.
He doesn't have to be
beside me the whole time
to know that we're good.
We're good.
- Everybody, group photo.
- I need him to slow his roll.
He is not guaranteed this.
I have a lot of other
relationships that are
really great, too.
But I don't think he gets it.
- Beautiful.
[upbeat music]
- Thank you so much,
all of you today.
I know how these group dates
are kind of goofy and silly,
but you'll always
just roll with it with me.
So let's make a toast
to opening up to each other
and to having a great night.
- Cheers.
[glasses clinking]
- Ah!
- Cheers.
- Luke P.,
do you wanna go talk?
- Yes, I would love to.
- Okay, let's go.
- You can just take my arm
or my hand.
- I'm confused.
What was that all--
what was that all about?
- It's possible that Hannah
wanted to get
a serious conversation
with him out of the way.
She almost--she almost
had real frustration.
- I kinda--Yeah.
[overlapping chatter]
A little bit, yeah.
- Today was a lot of fun,
but Luke P. stole the show
again but in a negative way.
♪ ♪
I know he's definitely one
of my strongest connections,
but, like, it's annoying
when Luke P., like,
tries to flaunt our connection
in front of the guys.
- [laughs]
- There have just been some,
like, little red flags
about how he carries himself
that bothers me a little bit.
It's, like, this fine line
of, like,
I really think is attractive
to, like, it's
the most unattractive thing
I've ever seen in my life.
- You have been amazing today,
seriously.
I mean, I look at you, and you
are beyond special to me.
And you do fit,
like, the perfect mold
of what I've been wanting
my whole life in a future wife.
And here I am
letting other guys
develop a stronger connection
and a stronger relationship
with you,
and I get to see you put your--
Everything you have in each and
every individual relationship.
I don't know, I just--
I really don't think
these guys...
just have what it takes
to be your future husband.
- You know I like you.
- Yes, I do.
- And that's great
and I'm glad that we, like,
automatically
had a deep connection,
but I've been struggling
a little bit with it
because I just feel like you
already think it's, like,
promised to you,
and that bothers me a lot.
And, like, I feel like
your confidence in this
kind of makes me irritated,
in a way.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, look, can I just
cut you off for a second?
Honestly, I'm happy we're
having this conversation.
- Yeah, hold on.
Let me talk.
- All right, sorry.
- Um...
I don't--like--like--
like, I want you to, like,
focus on me, and you do that,
but you also don't respect
that I do have
other relationships here,
like, for me,
and that bothers me.
[tense music]
I like confidence,
but it's, like, cocky in a way.
I don't like that at all.
- Okay.
- Okay?
♪ ♪
- I got you.
- I want it to change.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- So earlier today,
she hasn't handed out a rose
to anybody yet.
What do you think's gonna
determine who gets it, though?
- I think the guys
that have been patient
and have been respectful are
doing better with Hannah now
than the other guys, you know,
and there's a reason for that.
- What's up, dude?
- [sighs] Just--
Just chillin'.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, great.
- What's wrong?
What happened?
- I really only got
a few minutes with her,
and she was talking to me
most of the time.
But she told me
that she was irritated
with our relationship.
I don't know
if that's been going on
or that was just today.
And I haven't
really had the chance
to explain myself
all that much with her as well.
[tense music]
Hannah told me that...
she's irritated
with how I'm acting.
I'm coming off arrogant
and just too confident,
and I don't feel like
I've been acting that way.
I don't see her
seeing me like that.
It doesn't make sense to me.
I just want to continue
to move on.
I'm gonna act like the
conversation never happened.
- You look gorgeous, as always.
- Thank you.
- By the way, I love your
dress, or your romper.
- Thank you, romper.
- Romper.
- Yeah, it's okay if you
don't know what a romper is.
- [laughs]
No, I do. I do.
Have you seen the men rompers
that they had out,
like, a few years ago?
- Hey.
- Like,
three more minutes, man.
Just give me three more minutes
to finish out the conversation.
- I just need to get
something off my chest
with her real quick.
- Just...I will talk
to you later, okay?
[tense music]
- All right.
- All right, thank you.
Um...
- Luke P. was a little
shell-shocked tonight.
He kind of thought he was
in control amongst this group,
but then he saw the way
you and Hannah interacted...
- Uh-huh.
- And it rocked the boat.
- What's up?
- How are ya?
- I'm good. How are you?
- Good.
- It's good to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
- Thank you.
- Are we going over here?
- Come on back here.
- Hannah's gonna see
if you're acting desperately
and aggressively
in a bad way,
and there's a fine line
between bold and desperate.
- I'm very impressed.
- Thank you.
[tense music]
- What's up, man?
- How you doing?
♪ ♪
- Good. Can I have, like,
just a few more minutes?
We're talking
about something...
- You guys almost wrapped up?
- Just kinda personal, yeah.
[dramatic music]
- Yeah, sure.
♪ ♪
- [crunching loudly]
- I think Luke's
slowly self-imploding,
but that's just my opinion.
- Just a little bit.
But I would not be in his shoes
acting like that.
- He's very unstable right now.
Actually, I'm a little worried
about him.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, are you trying
to talk to Hannah?
- Yeah.
- All right,
that's not gonna
happen right now.
- I've been waiting a long
time, and I'm tired of it.
Just give me a minute.
- I haven't talked to her.
- You haven't?
- No.
- Well...
- Have you talked to her yet?
- Literally, I haven't either.
- So how do you--
I thought she grabbed you.
- Yeah, yeah, she did.
She explained herself to me,
but I didn't have time
to talk to her at all.
She talked to me,
and I see you,
like, standing here like
you're about to intercept her.
- I wasn't trying
to intercept her, dude.
I was just literally
trying to talk to her.
- I'm just not an idiot, okay?
- I'm not
saying you're an idiot.
- Yeah, you and I are cool.
- I know, we're super cool.
That's why
I don't get this right now.
- I'm not gonna
just let that happen.
That's why I'm standing here
right now.
- I get, like,
confronted by Luke P.,
and he's just like,
"Yo, bro, like"--
What? Like, what
is your problem right now?
I'm just trying--I haven't
even talked to her yet.
I'm pursuing Hannah.
Get over it.
- Seriously?
- He's, like, self-imploding.
This guy wants
to sink his own ship,
I am not gonna get in his way.
- This right here is annoying.
[dramatic chords]
[gentle music]
- You are so funny today.
- Well, thank you.
That was actually
a lot of fun today.
It was a lot of exposure.
- I appreciate it, though.
Thank you,
and I'm glad you're here.
♪ ♪
- I just want
to talk to Hannah.
- Yeah, I feel the same way.
You wanna go in and talk?
- I promise I'm gonna
talk to you again, but...
I don't--I don't wanna
do this right now, okay?
Let me talk to everybody.
But, like, I want to,
like, call my own shots.
Okay?
- You want to what?
- I want to call my own shots.
I said I was gonna talk to you.
- Yeah, okay.
- And I will talk to you again.
- All right.
- Okay?
- I got you.
- Hey.
- How you doing?
- What's up?
- You wanna talk?
- Yes.
- All right.
You're looking good.
- Thank you.
- I love this.
- Come on--
- I know, let's go
explore this place.
This is pretty sweet.
We have a tree in,
like, our courtyard.
- Let's go to...
we'll go to this one.
- All right, let's do it.
- I would be ecstatic
to get that rose tonight.
I feel like I,
in more than one way,
showed that I was willing
to do anything for Hannah.
- How are you doing?
Like, how are you
feeling right now?
You seem
a little unnerved right now.
- Because, honestly,
I can't stand this process.
Honestly, it's tough for me.
I'd like to say
that I'm the strong guy here
and this is easy,
but it's not.
Like, I even--
dude, I even had thoughts
about leaving here tonight,
about going home tonight.
- Wait, what?
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Why did you think
about going home tonight?
- Just because I can't say
that I'm in love with her.
I mean, if I did feel that way,
then I would be ready
to, you know,
get down on the knee.
- I just don't think
that Luke P.
is equipped to handle
this type of situation.
Could see the steam
kind of coming off his head,
he was so upset that things
weren't going his way.
Hey, man, if you're not ready
for this, go home.
- I'm just ready to see
if she really is that,
'cause if I do find out
that she's not
and I feel strongly that
she's not, I'm out of here.
- Yeah, I just had
a really good time.
- I had a really good time too.
- I truly enjoyed that.
- I like--I like
hanging out with you.
- I do too.
Um--yeah, no.
As Miss, like, Alabama,
you for sure have, like,
some photo shoot skills.
You know,
my mom was Miss Illinois.
- No!
- Yeah, she was
a pageant queen.
- I did not know that.
- Yep, and, like, I just--
- I like your mama.
[laughs]
- You got to meet my mom.
She's--Yeah, you guys
would get along for sure, so...
- How'd your mom
and your dad meet?
- Funny story.
- Uh-huh.
- My dad was a pilot as well.
- Yeah.
- My mom was
a flight attendant.
And she was on
his flight one time,
and he was walking back
to the cockpit
and he walked past her
and she just saw his butt,
and she goes to her friend,
she's like, "That's the guy
I'm gonna marry."
I swear to God.
- From the butt?
- Just from his butt.
Yeah, so literally from there,
they hit it off, and, boom,
however many years later,
here I am.
- Yeah.
- And talking
to Miss Hannah Brown.
Every time I see you, like,
I leave just feeling so happy
and, like, I can't
stop thinking about you
and I love that.
Like, it's crazy.
- I love that too.
[laughs]
- Yeah, it's like--like,
right now,
like, this couldn't be
going better for me, so...
- Good, I'm glad.
- I'm super happy.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
I'm falling very hard
for Hannah Kelsey Brown.
She just makes you feel
so good and just so comforting
and just, like, inspires you
to be a better person,
and she's just so sweet.
Like that little
giggle she does,
and just, like,
the twinkle in her eye.
It sounds, like, so cheesy,
but I love it.
♪ ♪
Oh, I'm so happy.
Like, this is awesome.
That could be
my wife right there.
That really could.
Oh, my God.
That was the smoothest
takeoff I've ever had,
and this is gonna be
the greatest flight of my life,
like, for sure.
- All right.
- There she is.
[low chatter]
- Come on in.
- I just love all the smells.
It's so nice.
[laughter]
I'm sorry, it's really fun.
Thank y'all so much,
all of you.
Um...
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Luke, can we just talk
for one minute really quick?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- That was weird.
- No way.
- He's definitely
gonna get the rose...
- You think so?
- 'Cause she grabbed the rose.
- Yeah, I mean,
she left with it.
- That would be disappointing.
- [whispers]
I really like you, okay?
I still don't feel like
you're getting it, okay?
You are not
the only relationship here
that I have
a strong connection with,
and I don't feel like you've
respected that, even tonight.
So I just need you to work
harder and fix this, okay?
- Definitely. Thank you for
letting me know how you feel.
'Cause I would feel robbed
if you didn't
communicate that with me,
so I'm very appreciative.
And now I know
what I need to do, so...
Thank you.
Can I have a hug?
- Sorry.
Peter, I had the best time
with you tonight,
and every time
that we are together,
I feel like our relationship
grows more and more,
and tonight
was definitely my favorite.
So, Peter...
- Yes?
- Will you accept this rose?
- I would love to.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
Thank you.
You look really good.
- You look good too.
Well, I'm gonna go to sleep,
'cause you know I was
in the hospital yesterday.
[laughter]
- You need your sleep.
- Um, you're the best, yeah.
- See you tomorrow night?
- Yeah, yeah.
Bye.
- Good night.
- I'm feeling good.
It was a good day.
For sure, I won't
forget that anytime soon.
Excited to see
where this could go.
[dramatic music]
- Coming up...
- Cam told us that he was
gonna tell you a sad story
to kind of get a pity rose.
- This just feels
really schemy and slimy to me.
♪ ♪
- Mike planted
the seed in her mind,
and I'm very pissed off.
I don't need anybody's pity.
- Whoa.
- What just happened?
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I'm stoked
for the cocktail party.
- Tonight, just gotta
make the most of it.
- Definitely.
- Just make the most
of the time you got with her
and be confident in that time.
I'm excited for tonight.
I just can't wait to see her
and see that smile
and see those two dimples
and keeping this thing rolling.
- Hello.
What's up, boys?
- Mr. Chris.
- Chris!
- How we doing?
- Great.
- Fantastic.
- Good to see you.
Obviously, you guys
know what's going on tonight.
Gonna be a Rose Ceremony.
But I came here to let you know
that there will not
be a cocktail party.
- What?
- But you know
she's from Alabama.
You know she loves
Bama football.
Well, what's Bama football
without a tailgate party?
[all cheering]
- Yeah!
[upbeat rock music]
- Tailgate, let's go!
- So gonna be a blast.
Have a good time.
Show her a good time.
- All right.
- See you guys later.
- All right,
see you later, Chris.
- Today really is
make it or break it.
I feel that my experience here
could be in jeopardy
because I don't have
a rose right now,
so A-B-C, Always Be Cam.
That's all I can do
in this moment.
Hey, y'all, hey, guys, guys.
Um...
I need to say something
pretty serious.
Uh, obviously,
I was expecting there to be
a cocktail party tonight,
and there's something
very, very personal
and very serious in my life
that I need
to discuss with Hannah
that I haven't
had an opportunity to.
And this has been
something that has been
a downfall in my past
two serious relationships.
So right when it gets started,
I need to just pull her aside
for a second and, you know,
there's a strong likelihood
that it may be too much
for her to handle
and she sends me home
even before the Rose Ceremony.
I just want to say
it's been an absolute privilege
getting to know each
and every one of you guys.
You know, metaphorical cheers
to, you know,
living your truth,
and that's really all I'll say.
- BS, no.
There's no rules of engagement.
[tense music]
- True but, you know...
Anyways.
- Cam is one of those guys
who has not been respectful,
and now he wants us
to respect him
and to give him the first go.
It's infuriating.
It's frickin'
pissing everybody off.
[upbeat music]
- Hey, girl's here!
- Tailgate!
[all cheering]
- This is like home for me.
[all cheer]
- Let's go!
- You can't beat
having a tailgate.
The guys are all hanging.
We're throwing footballs...
[both grunt]
We're throwing cornhole.
- Oh, there, you got one!
- Hannah doesn't
have to do a damn thing
to look absolutely
breathtaking.
- Yeah!
Today's about having fun,
because I've had a hard week.
I mean, heck, I visited
the hospital this week.
I just want
easy conversations.
I don't want to hear
about anything tragic.
I just need a chill day.
- I got a--I got a quick thing
I wanna run by you real quick.
You down for that?
- Okay, yeah.
- Let's go.
- Oh, thank you.
- How's your day going?
Did you get some rest, finally?
- Yeah.
- I'm a little POed.
Honestly, I am,
because Cam, once again,
grabbed Hannah's attention
away from everyone.
Once again, it was just
another calculated move by Cam.
- So I wanted to bring you
over here because, you know,
in all of our previous
conversations,
I keep alluding to, you know,
I'm an onion
with a lot of layers.
- Mm-hmm.
- And considering
how precious time is
and, you know, I wanted
to get a chance to talk to you
before tonight's Rose Ceremony.
Just a little forewarning.
Like, this is not an easy
conversation for me to have,
but back in the year 2014,
I was getting off work
and, um, all of a sudden,
my right leg locked up on me.
And all of a sudden,
I was running a fever,
and they had to rush me
to the hospital.
Essentially, they told me that
I needed to get an amputation.
- Oh, my gosh.
- So...
life really tried
to beat me down.
- I'm a little annoyed
with Cam.
This is--it's not a party
without Hannah here.
- I mean, we should be having
fun with Hannah, right?
- Yeah.
- Why are we giving Cam
so much [bleep bleep] time?
- We can't have one person just
sap up our day with Hannah,
you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- The day before I got surgery,
I got a call from my dad that
my grandma had passed away.
- Hannah, coming into this,
you know, she was like
a big ball of energy.
And Cam, I feel like,
is hitting her
with some
down [bleep] right now.
- Yeah.
- The most recent surgery
that I had
in November of 2017
hit me the hardest
because I actually had
a ten-month-old puppy
at the time
that I was super close to
that I had to rehome.
- I mean, Hannah knows all the
stuff that Cam's pulled, right?
- We were on a group date,
and he was trying to butt in
on two different people's
conversations.
Like, why wasn't it said then,
like, if it was that important?
- And, you know,
you have such a big heart
and I know we haven't had
too much time to talk,
but I can see that,
and I'm so happy to be here.
I didn't want to go
in tonight's Rose Ceremony
without being
fully transparent with you
and giving you the full picture
of who I am.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much, Hannah.
You're an amazing woman.
- Oh, thank you.
- Let's go have some fun, yeah?
- Let's do it.
- Coming into
this tailgate party,
you know, I had a lot
of anxiety about, you know,
how Hannah would respond to me
laying it all on the line.
I couldn't have asked
for a better response.
- Cam, did you say
what you had to say?
- Yeah, I did, and she--
she responded really well.
- Cam, I think his back's
against the wall a little bit.
Simple as that.
- Yeah, everything he does
is pretty much choreographed
at this point.
I think Cam is being
manipulative against Hannah
'cause he feel like
he's gonna be cut.
If I continue to get
disrespected by somebody,
I'm gonna make sure
that you get booted.
Cam is working his ass off
for a pity rose
just to stay here
another week,
and so I'ma tell Hannah about
all his [bleep bleep].
[upbeat music]
- Say go!
[laughs]
- Oh!
- You dropped it.
- Today was a really pretty day
for a tailgate.
- Hannah, we gotta take some
stress out today, all right?
- [gasps] Yes!
- Come on.
- Today had to be about me
feeling comfortable.
Sun was out.
- So I was a tight end,
as you can tell.
- Buns were out.
- Wanna feel it?
Behave, girl. Behave.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
tight end.
Cute buns.
- Bring the beast right now,
all right?
Ready?
One, two, three.
- [screams]
[laughter]
K.O.--knocked out.
I'm good. I'm good.
Good thing he's good-lookin'
and cute.
- How's your tailgate going?
- It's going great.
My conversations with the guys
are really great.
The conversations
were lighter and fun,
and that is what
Mama needs today.
- So I have a question for you.
- Yeah.
- How was, uh, it for you
being in the mansion
and...just seeing what goes on?
How was that for you?
How did you react to that?
- Uh, I don't know.
I felt like Colton did
a really good job of, um,
kind of knowing who was here,
you know, for the right reasons
and who was, you know,
truly who they said they were,
and it's really hard for--
Now I completely get it.
- Um...
earlier when Chris came by...
- Mm-hmm.
- After he left,
Cam sat us all down and told us
that he was gonna
tell you a sad story
to kind of get the pity rose,
a sad story that would
keep his time here longer.
He was basically
doing Dear John letters
to the other guys, thinking
that he was going home,
and I'm only telling you
because that's something
that you should know.
- Yeah.
- We were just saying
it's kind of forced.
- It's like his, like, last
effort Hail Mary-type thing.
Like, you know, you want people
to, like, tell you things
and it be because they, like,
have a connection with you
and, like, it be genuine,
not because they think
they're going home
and just want to be here
and be a part of this...
Because, at that point,
it doesn't become about me.
It becomes
about staying around...
- Correct.
- And getting roses.
- Right.
- I'm really disappointed.
You know,
Cam was the very first guy
I ever gave a rose to.
Give me a hug.
I really did appreciate
Cam being vulnerable,
but I feel like
what Cam did today
was a little manipulative.
That is just
really disheartening
because this is my life,
this is my future,
and I don't give pity roses.
Uh, Cam, can we go talk?
- [exhales]
[bleep], dude.
[dramatic music]
- Everything okay?
- Just talk for a second.
- Okay.
- What just happened, fellas?
- Uh, that was not good.
That was not good.
- She was about to cry.
- She--she was,
like, really emotional.
♪ ♪
- I first want to say, uh...
I did appreciate you telling me
what you did today,
but I just had a conversation
with Mike,
and...
was told that, you know,
you thought you were
going home this morning
and let all the guys know,
and I just feel like it's...
an interesting time
for you to bring up this story
in, like, a ditch effort
to stay.
And so I'm just--you know,
I wanna know if that's true
and just, yeah.
- Sure, sure, yeah.
So this morning, I did want
to make it clear to guys
that I did have
something very serious
that I wanted
to talk to you about.
- Well, I heard a pity rose.
- Pity rose?
I would never
compromise the integrity
of what I've been through
for a pity rose.
Like, this is--
this is a serious thing.
This is a very serious thing.
- It--it--no, the sto--
what you told me
is very serious,
but it feels very manipulative
at the timing of it
with what I've heard,
what happened this morning,
that you were
writing letters to guys
'cause you thought you were
going home, is that true?
- I was writing letters.
- So you thought
you were going home
and felt like
you needed to tell--
- I never said I thought
I was going home.
- Why were you writing letters?
- Huh?
- Then why were you
writing letters?
- I was writing letters because
I didn't know how you
would respond to this.
- So then you did think
you were going home.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- The Rose Ceremony's
in a couple of hours,
and we didn't have
the cocktail party.
This was the cocktail party.
- This is not about just
getting roses and staying.
This just feels really schemy
and slimy to me.
It just seems
really, really calculated, of--
[tense music]
- So it sounds like you don't--
that you don't trust me.
- I'm having a hard time
right now,
and I just--I need
to think about it and--
- Hannah, I want
to build our relationship,
and it's hard for me--
- Just--just--
Let me just
think about it, okay?
- I respect that.
- Yeah.
- This is my worst nightmare.
I feel pretty hurt
for what transpired today.
Right now, my integrity
is in question.
Oh, God, okay.
[crying]
This is the [bleep] feeling,
and if I go home because of it,
I'm gonna be devastated.
- Hate to steal you away,
but it is time
for the Rose Ceremony.
- Oh.
Um, thank you guys so much.
Know that I have some
difficult decisions to make,
and if you get a rose,
it is not a pity rose.
Look forward
to seeing you tonight.
Thank you again.
- You fellas go get dressed.
We'll see you
at the Rose Ceremony.
- All right.
- I would say
that Cam feels very nervous.
Hannah saying that she's not
going to give out a pity rose,
she gave him a warning shot,
for sure.
Maybe he'll get a rose,
and I would be
surprised if he did,
but, you know,
you never know.
Hannah, I think,
at the end of the day,
her choices come down
to the connections
that she forms.
She might give him
another chance.
[dramatic music]
- You know, time will tell,
and it's Hannah's choice
at the end of the night,
so we'll have to just see.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Earlier today,
Hannah turned her head to Cam
and said, "There will be
no pity roses tonight."
You know, I kinda
read into that as,
Cam's getting a rose
and it's not gonna be out
of pity of what he did today.
Some people are reading
into it as,
Cam's not gonna get a rose
because he tried
to get a pity rose.
I really think it's gonna
surprise a lot of people
and he's gonna
get a rose tonight.
- I'm terrified
going into tonight.
someone tarnished
my intentions
without even knowing
a damn thing about my past.
It's incredibly frustrating
to know that my destiny
with Hannah and this journey
is at the mercy of her
choosing to believe me.
- [exhales]
- Ooh.
- Wow.
- [laughs]
- Goodness gracious.
- Can we say you look amazing?
- Yes, please?
- Yeah, you can tell me
all day long.
[laughter]
- Um...
Thank you guys so much
for an incredible day today.
Uh...
It gets harder and harder
every single week
to stand up here
in front of you guys
and make these decisions.
Know that if you
don't get a rose tonight,
it was a hard decision,
but I have to go
with my heart,
and I am confident
in my decisions.
For those of you
that are still here,
I'm really excited
about our future.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Jed.
Jed, will you accept this rose?
- You know I will.
♪ ♪
- Tyler.
Tyler, will you
accept this rose?
- Always.
- I think if Cam got a rose
tonight and I went home,
I would obviously
be pissed off.
He is calculated.
- Dustin.
♪ ♪
Dustin, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
♪ ♪
- Dylan.
Dylan, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
- Last night at
the group date, I screwed up.
I definitely lost
a lot of confidence.
She just pretty much
communicated
kinda things that she wanted
to see out of me.
- Grant.
♪ ♪
- So I really wanna
get a chance
to be able to prove
myself to her.
- Will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- I need to get
that rose tonight.
♪ ♪
- Luke P.
Luke, will you
accept this rose?
- Without a doubt.
♪ ♪
- Garrett.
Garrett, will you
accept this rose?
- I sure will.
♪ ♪
- John Paul Jones.
John Paul Jones,
will you accept this rose?
- With gratitude.
♪ ♪
- Matteo.
Matteo, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
- I didn't get that one-on-one
time tonight again
because of Cam's shenanigans,
and to not get a rose
just because
I didn't get to talk with her,
that's awful.
- Devin.
♪ ♪
Devin, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
- Hannah is in a position.
Does she believe Mike J.,
who says that I'm here
for a pity rose,
or is she gonna have
some faith in me?
♪ ♪
- Luke S.
- I would never use this
as leverage.
That was absolutely
the most devastating thing
that I've ever heard
in my entire life.
- Luke, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
- If I go home
because of this,
there will be
a lot of bitterness.
- Hannah, gentlemen,
this is the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Kevin.
Kevin, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
take a moment,
say your good-byes.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- Good luck, guys.
Take care.
- It's been real.
I had a great time with you.
- Thank you.
- Be good to these guys
all right?
- I'll try.
- Take care.
- Joe.
♪ ♪
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you, Jonathan.
- Your husband's in this room.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Thanks for the opportunity.
I really do hope that you find
what you're looking for.
- Thank you.
- Guys.
[solemn music]
It's a tough pill to swallow
to hear someone
that you pour your heart
out to call you calculated.
It sucks because
if she truly knew Cam,
she would know
that's not in my nature.
[tearfully] I came out here
with the best of intentions.
I still can't believe
that...
when I was as most vulnerable
as I've ever been
that people were
questioning my integrity.
[somber music]
[sniffles]
- I am looking forward
to this next week
of new adventures
and to finding love.
So cheers.
- Cheers to you, Hannah.
- Cheers.
[glasses clinking]
- Next week on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss!
[overlapping shouting]
- ♪ And the rocket's
red glare ♪
Pow! Pow!
[all cheering]
- Your, like, energy
is so, like, contagious.
- Newsflash--
Peter's my boyfriend.
- I wanna be the guy
at the end of the day.
I wanna be with you.
- I feel something
growing inside me
that I never felt before,
and I think it could
turn into forever.
- Oh!
- And then...
♪ ♪
- You're violent.
You're aggressive.
You are a psychopath.
- Why does every single
guy here dislike you?
- We all know that Luke P's
an evil pathological liar.
- Let me just tell you, man.
Karma is a bitch,
and you're gonna get yours.
- Your story has changed.
I feel like you think that
I'm a threat to you,
'cause I am the biggest threat
against you right now.
- I'm not threatened
by anybody...
especially not you.
- Somebody mess with my queen,
I need to take
that person down.
- [sniffling]
[siren wailing]
- And later this season...
- I don't care what
you said to her.
I've been nothing but truthful,
and you are not gonna
mess it up!
- Stop [bleep] with my mind.
- I just don't fully understand
how you can be as amazing
as you are
and consider someone
like him.
- Where I'm from,
we call that [bleep].
- There have been some people
questioning Hannah.
- [sobbing]
[thunder rumbling]
I don't owe you anything
at this point.
Just stop!
My husband would never say
what you said to me.
You don't own me.
You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do
because, first of all,
you're not my husband,
and even my husband,
the person I'm gonna be with,
is gonna allow me
to be my own person.
Get the [bleep] away from me.
I believe that sex was made
for a man and a woman
in marriage, but I'm having
physical relationships,
so, like, I have had sex.
And, honestly...
Jesus still loves me.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Be my friend.
- Como esta?
- What do we need to do here?
- I think it's a great match,
but I feel like--can you
stand up for a moment?
- Let's see that--
- I feel we need to--
Mm!
- Hm...
- Maybe we should do
a little waxing on you.
- Yeah, let's do it--okay.
- Oh, my gosh.
Franco and Hannah
decided that
I need to resemble my dog
a little bit more,
so, yeah, they, uh...
they waxed me.
- Drop it on the right side.
- That feels good.
Feels good...
Aah! Oh!
- Ah, yes!
Garrett thrives
in the pain.
Kinda like that.
He was like, "Bring it on."
Right on the nipple.
- Bring it.
Come on!
Bring it.
- One, two, three.
- Yes!
Aah ha ha ha!
Feels good!
- You are strong!
- Right there.
- Oh...
Ooh...
yeah!
- Oh, yeah.
Nice!
- I deserve this freaking
rose big-time.
Yeah.
- Now you look like Laverne.